<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mission on Learney Blog - Knowledge aggregator for developers</title>
    <link>https://blog.learney.io/tags/mission/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mission on Learney Blog - Knowledge aggregator for developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 07:48:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.learney.io/tags/mission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Mission of Learney</title>
      <link>https://blog.learney.io/post/about-the-mission-of-learney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 07:48:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.learney.io/post/about-the-mission-of-learney/</guid>
      <description>Every founder of every new public initiative or project at some point needs to answer this one question. Question about conquering the world.
People ask me “How does Learney want to compete with Twitter, Medium, HackerNews or Facebook groups where we already look for knowledge?” That’s a really good question, but my answer may surprise you a bit.
Why? Because I don’t want to compete with them. That’s not even my long-term goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it worth to share the knowledge?</title>
      <link>https://blog.learney.io/post/knowledge-sharing-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 19:16:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.learney.io/post/knowledge-sharing-values/</guid>
      <description>One of the main goals of Learney is to make sharing the knowledge easy and fun. Some of you may agree with the importance of such a mission, but others will ask - why does it really matter?
Today I’d like you to give you some example values that knowledge sharing brings to the table when it’s a part of your daily routine.
It helps you become a better teacher Knowledge sharing may be realized through many different forms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>