<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Learney Blog - Knowledge aggregator for developers</title>
    <link>https://blog.learney.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Learney Blog - Knowledge aggregator for developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 19:16:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.learney.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it worth to share the knowledge?</title>
      <link>https://blog.learney.io/post/knowledge-sharing-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 19:16:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.learney.io/post/knowledge-sharing-values/</guid>
      <description>One of the main goals of Learney is to make sharing the knowledge easy and fun. Some of you may agree with the importance of such a mission, but others will ask - why does it really matter?
Today I’d like you to give you some example values that knowledge sharing brings to the table when it’s a part of your daily routine.
It helps you become a better teacher Knowledge sharing may be realized through many different forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First week, live!</title>
      <link>https://blog.learney.io/post/first-week-passed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 20:28:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.learney.io/post/first-week-passed/</guid>
      <description>Such a week! Only ten days passed since Learney has launched and tons of amazing things already happened. Let me share this short update with you to summarize everything and explain what’s on the roadmap for incoming weeks.
First and foremost - a few words about all that feedback you’ve been sending to me through that period. I’m really amazed how many people want to support this random project of a random guy who believes that knowledge sharing worths much more attention, especially in the context of software development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learney says Hello, World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.learney.io/post/learney-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 14:52:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.learney.io/post/learney-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>My name is Przemek, I’m a 25-year-old software engineer from Cracow, Poland. Since last few years, I’ve been focused on different aspects of knowledge sharing within our industry. One of my ongoing goals is to give back to the community through all kinds of activities like running a blog for aspiring developers, preparing conference talks, writing articles or contributing to open source.
By doing all of this not only I’m able to express my “thanks for everything” for other software developers but also learn about your day-to-day struggles related to gathering the knowledge, avoiding distractions and just becoming more competent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>